Are you fat? It's a simple yes to my question.
If yes, you'll need a calorie deficit.
If no, you can bypass that and go straight to lifting weights.
But once you've determined your calorie deficit,
you also need to lift weights.
And the next important question is, do you enjoy sport like proper sport, tennis or golf or jiu-jitsu or rugby or infeapple?
If you like sport, and you play sport, you go straight to the high protein diet.
But if you don't like sport, you get about three and a half thousand step counts a day.
Yeah, you're going to need some form of cardio.
Now, that could be taking the stairs, increasing your step count, maybe getting on a cross-trainer.
You could get on a spin bike, which is just cycling on a stationary bike with the brakes on.
Or you could get a real bike, or you could go for a run, you could go jogging, you could train for your first 5K.
You could even start swimming.
But when it comes to determining what type of cardio you should be doing, is a very simple formula.
Do you like the modality of training that you're doing?
If you're not enjoying the type of cardio that you're doing, well that's a problem.
And you need to go back up to the cardio stage and pick something that you actually enjoy.
When it comes to people sustaining and adhering stuff, humans don't like to do things they don't want to do.
And if they do do things they don't want to do, they don't do it very long.
But if you are finding a bit of cardio you like and you do enjoy it, well, you get to come over to the high protein diet section.
Which is about 1 to 2 grams of protein per day.
And also, if you are obese, you can go 1 gram of protein per centimeter in height.
And now you think we're a carbohydrate some fats.
Well, if you're a quake protein and you're quake calories, whether you go high carb, or low fat,
doesn't make a difference for far loss.